♪ Hello, it's me ♪
♪ I was wondering if
after all these years ♪
♪ You'd like to meet ♪
♪ To go over everything ♪
♪ They say that time's
supposed to heal ya ♪
♪ But I ain't done much healing ♪
♪ Hello, can you hear me ♪
♪ I'm in California dreaming
about who we used to be ♪
♪ When we were younger and free ♪
♪ I've forgotten how it felt ♪
♪ Before the world fell at our feet ♪
♪ There's such a difference between us ♪
♪ And a million miles ♪
♪ Hello from the other side ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done ♪
♪ But when I call, you
never seem to be home ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry
for breaking your heart ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't
tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ Hello, how are you ♪
♪ It's so typical of me to
talk about myself, I'm sorry ♪
♪ I hope that you're well ♪
♪ Did you ever make it out of that town ♪
♪ Where nothing ever happened ♪
♪ It's no secret that the both of us ♪
♪ Are running out of time ♪
♪ So hello from the other side ♪
♪ Other side ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ Thousand times ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done ♪
♪ But when I call, you
never seem to be home ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ Outside ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ I've tried ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry
for breaking your heart ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't
tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ Hello from the other side ♪
♪ Other side ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ Thousand times ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done ♪
♪ But when I call, you
never seem to be home ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ Outside ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ I've tried ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry
for breaking your heart ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't
tear you apart anymore ♪
(somber music)